let qustions=[
    {
        id:1,
        question:"Tap A can empty the tank in 20 hours. B and C can fill the same tank in 10 and 12 hours respectively. All the taps are opened simultaneously. Find the time required for the tank to get filled completely.",
        answer:"7 hours 30 minutes",
        option:[
            "9 hours 30 minutes",
            "7 hours 30 minutes",
            "7 hours 45 minutes",
            "10 hours 30 minutes",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:"Two pipes X and Y can fill a tank in 6 hours and 9 hours respectively. If they are turned on alternately for one hour each starting with X then what will be the time taken to fill the tank?",
        answer:"7 hours",
        option:[
            "6 hours",
            "7 hours",
            "8 hours",
            "9 hours",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:"Two pipes A and B can fill a tank in 18 and 36 hours respectively. An outlet pipe C can empty it in 24 hours. If they opened together, then in how many hours the 3/4th of the capacity of the tank is filled?",
        answer:"18 hours",
        option:[
            "22 hours",
            "24 hours",
            "18 hours",
            "19 hours",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:"There is a water tank which is 2/5th full. Pipe A can fill that tank in 4 hrs and pipe B can empty that tank in 6 hrs. If both pipes are open together, then find the time taken (in hrs.) to fill that tank completely?",
        answer:"7.2",
        option:[
            "8",
            "7.2",
            "9",
            "7.8",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:"Pipe A can fill the tank 2 times faster than pipe B and pipe C can fill the tank 3 times faster than pipe A. If pipe A can fill the tank in 15 minutes, then in how many minutes all the pipes fill the tank?",
        answer:"3 minutes 20 seconds",
        option:[
            "3 minutes 40 minutes",
            "3 minutes 30 seconds",
            "3 minutes 20 seconds",
            "3 minutes 45 seconds",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:"Three taps A, B, and C can fill a tank in 12 mins, 15 mins and 20 mins respectively. All the three taps are opened simultaneously. But due to some obstacles it was found that only 2/5th of water from A, 3/4th of water from B and 2/3rd of water from C flows through them. After removing the obstacles if was found that it takes 312 minutes to fill the tank. Find the time after which the obstacles were removed.",
        answer:"18/7",
        option:[
            "19/7",
            "18/7",
            "14/3",
            "12/3",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:"Pipe X fills a cistern of volume 3000 units in 4 hours. Pipe Y fills a cistern of 2500 units in 5 hours. How much time will both the pipes together take to fill a cistern of 4800 units?",
        answer:"3.84 hours",
        option:[
            "2 hours",
            "3.84 hours",
            "2.4 hours",
            "3.2 hours",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:"A tank can be filled by two pipes A and B in 4 hours. It can be filled by pipes B and C in 6 hours. How much time will A alone take to fill the tank, if all three of them fills the tank in 2 hours?",
        answer:"3 hours",
        option:[
            "5 hours",
            "4 hours",
            "6 hours",
            "3 hours",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:"Pipe A can fill the tank in 12 hours, Pipe B can fill the tank in 15 hours, While Pipe C can empty the tank. If all the pipes opened at once tank can be filled in 10 hours. Pipe C can empty 150 liters of a tank in 1 hour. Find the capacity of a tank in liters.",
        answer:"3000 litres",
        option:[
            "2500 litres",
            "4000 litres",
            "1800 litres",
            "3000 litres",
        ]
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:"Pipe P alone can fill the tank in 20 hours while Pipe Q can empty the tank in 30 hours. Pipe R alone can fill the tank in certain hours. If all three pipes are opened simultaneously for 5 hours and then pipe R is closed. Pipe P and Pipe Q takes 30 hours to fill the remaining tank. Pipe R alone can fill the tank in â€“",
        answer:"12 hours",
        option:[
            "12 hours",
            "40 hours",
            "46 hours",
            "18 hours",
        ]
    }
    
]